Um, okay, everyone.
A toast to this gathering
of friends new and old.
To us!
With everyone here, we'd
be an amazing party.
Yeah, we would. I know.
We should raid the boss on floor 23.
I'm down with that.
Then let's go get him.
Yeah!
You're going down!
The end of the day.
I was walking around the night.
If anything happens?
I'm happy to be here.
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Uh-oh!
Oh,
oh!
Yeah!
Thank you
so
much
for joining us today.
Ah!
Thank goodness, you made it.
About 40 minutes ago, her heart
stopped, but only for a moment.
We got it going with
defibrillation and meds.
But if it happens again…
Why now?
Why is this happening?
She seemed fine!
I'm sorry.
The truth is, ever since January,
when you first came to visit her,
her condition's been touch and go.
And for these last three months,
we've all been stunned by how
Yuki's managed to hang in there.
She can't beat this,
but she keeps fighting.
She keeps on fighting.
The 15 years Yuki spent on this
planet have been one long battle.
The HIV is only part of it.
She's also been fighting the harsh reality
of her situation while in treatment.
There's no doubt the
clinical trials with the
Medicuboid caused her an
unimaginable amount of pain.
And still, somehow Yuki keeps hanging on.
Well, anyway, we should
let her get some rest now.
Come on, Yuki.
You can't lose.
I mean, you're second.
The ultimate Swordsman.
Take her hand.
It's okay.
That's what she wants.
Doctor, can she use the Medicuboid now?
But, well, wouldn't she want
to spend her last moments here?
No, she wants to go back one last time.
Please, Doctor, let her
use the Medicuboid again.
It's going to take about
a minute to boot up.
Then what?
I'm going next door to
log in with the Amusphere.
Wait for me, Yuki.
I'm coming.
Thanks, Asuna.
I'm glad I got to see you again,
because I got something for you.
I can't believe I almost
forgot about it. Really?
What is it you wanted to give me?
Oh, um, I still gotta make it.
Hang on a sec.
Ahhhhhhh!
Yuki!
that's weird i feel so
weak all of a sudden
i'm not in any pain or
anything though it's
okay you're just a little
tired is all you'll
feel better if you rest
yeah maybe listen Asuna
Take this.
It's my original sword skill.
No, Yuki, I couldn't.
Oh, come on.
I want you to have it.
Open the window.
I gave it a cool name.
Mother's Rosario.
It'll keep you safe.
When you need it.
Thank you, Yuki.
I promise.
I'll take good care of it.
And someday, when I leave this world,
I'll make sure to pass it
on to someone before I go.
Your sword will live on
until the end of time.
Thank you.
Oh guys, come on.
We talked about this.
You promised.
No goodbyes.
Nah, you got it wrong.
We're all here to cheer you up.
When you get to the other
side, wait for us, okay?
We won't take too long, promise.
What are you talking about?
If you get there too soon, I'll be pissed.
You know the deal.
You're hopeless without us.
So don't even try to argue.
Just sit tight and wait.
For...
for us.
Please, Nori, don't cry.
We promised we'd be strong.
I give up.
You win.
I'll wait for you.
But take your time.
You got it?
Look at all those fairies.
I'm sorry.
I had to let them know.
I hope you're not mad at me.
Are you kidding?
Why would I be mad?
There's so many of them.
It's like a dream.
Why are they here?
Because of you.
You're the strongest, most powerful
Swordsman this world's ever seen.
There will never be anyone
else like you again.
We can't let you go
without saying goodbye.
It's not right.
We're all praying for you.
That your next journey will be
to a place as wonderful as this.
I'm happy.
I'm so happy.
You know this whole time I thought
if I was born to die what the heck
was the point of me even Being born I
never made anything or gave anything
to anyone all I did was waste drugs
and hog that Machine and cause
trouble for everyone if all I get to
do is suffer and disappear in the end
It'd be better to just disappear right
now I used to always think why am I alive
Why do I stick around for
this long but you know
what after all this time
I think I know why now
I might not have done much But
I'm glad I got to live Cause
after everything These last few
moments They're the best ever
I'm surrounded by all
my friends And I got to
end my journey In the
arms of someone I love
Yuki I promise I will
see you again someday
in some other place
some other world I don't
know How but I'll find
you and then we can sit
and talk and you can
tell me where you've been
I gave this life.
Everything I had.
I was alive.
¶¶
I never made anything, or
gave anything to anyone.
You gave me something.
You carved it deep into my
heart, and it'll always be there.
Hello, Asuna.
How are you?
Wait, is that you, Siyone?
Yes, in the flesh.
It's nice to finally meet
you in the real world.
I'm Sheen Ahn.
Oh, it's nice to see you, too.
I'm Asuna Yuki.
Like meeting for the first time, huh?
But no, it's okay.
Just this month I got
the all clear from my
doctor and was discharged
from the hospital.
Then you're doing better?
Yes
The type of disease I have is
called acute lymphocytic leukemia.
And it was about three years
ago when I developed it.
The side effects from the
medicine were so horrible!
I wanted to die rather
than keep suffering.
But whenever I saw Yuki, I thought,
here's this kid, and she's handling her
situation better than I'm handling mine.
Around February, they started
cutting back on the meds I was on.
I thought, this is it, and
I braced myself for the end.
And then a week ago, the day after
Yuki died, my doctor came in and said,
congratulations, you're
in complete remission.
Next thing I knew, I was being discharged.
I barely had a chance to process the news.
And the truth is, it
still hasn't sunk in yet.
It's like, I should feel awful.
It doesn't seem fair that I'm
still here and Yuki's waiting.
Yuki and Ron, Clovis and Merida, we
promised we'd stick together forever.
And I'm here.
Sheen.
You know,
our lives are like vessels,
and we carry the teachings of
the ones who've passed in them.
For the longest time, I was so scared.
Scared of telling someone
how I really felt,
and scared of finding out how they felt.
But I learned from Yuki that
that was no way for me to live.
If I didn't even try to reach
out, nothing would ever change.
She taught me how to be strong, and
I want to share that with others.
As long as I'm alive, I'll pass on what
I learned from her to everyone I meet.
And then someday,
when I see her again, I want to tell
her about all the people she's helped.
That's how I'll pay her back.
Thank you, Asuna.
You know, we're all so
grateful for what you've done.
I'd been so worried about Yuki.
She was carrying a heavy burden
on those little shoulders of hers.
But then you showed up, and
something in her changed.
When you were together, Yuki seemed
like she was really having fun.
She was like a forgetful bird
who remembered how to fly.
Then she flew up and up, and
now she's out of our reach.
Anyway, June's also doing great.
The medication he's on
seems to be working.
It's like, I don't know,
to me it feels like Yuki's telling all
of us it's still too soon to join her.
I guess that means it's
going to be a while yet
before the sleeping
knights get back together.
Just remember,
next time you're taking me in as a member
and I don't want to hear any arguments.
Hey.
I hope we're not interrupting anything.
No.
But wait, do you guys
know each other? Sort of.
He's trying to steal my ideas about
that communications pod I made.
No, he's lying.
I'm interested in its possibilities
in full-dive medical tech,
so we've been emailing back and forth.
That's great for both of you.
What about the medicuboid?
Are you going to phase it out,
or were the trials successful?
Glad you asked.
They were extremely successful,
and now we have enough data
to proceed to the next phase.
Soon patients all over
the country will have...
I am so sorry about that.
I can't believe I didn't say this first.
Mizan, congratulations on your recovery.
I know Yuki would be
thrilled at the news too.
Thank you for saying so.
And congratulations on the trials.
It's good to know what you learned
from Yuki will be used to help others.
That makes me happy. Me too.
Yuki was the first person
to test the medicuboid,
and her name will always be remembered.
If she were here, she'd
get an award for her help,
along with the benefactor
who made it all possible.
Knowing Yuki, she wouldn't be
too thrilled at getting an award.
She'd say, what's the point in
having it if I can't eat it?
Um, Doctor, you just mentioned the
Medicuboid had some kind of benefactor.
I thought you said the
government was paying for it.
Oh, well, yes, they are.
But the initial designs were given
to us for free from someone else.
If I remember correctly,
I think her name was Dr.
Rank Kojiro.
What's wrong, Kirito?
I know her.
How?
I met her once.
Yeah, in fact, she was taking care of
Heathcliff's body while he was diving.
She was his head researcher.
She helped him develop
full dive technology.
You see?
The Medicuboid's design.
You know who invented it?
No way.
It was Kayaba.
I want to show you what
I want
to
show you.
I will always be able to make sure.
I don't know when I'm wrong.
I will be able to see you. I will be able
to see
you?
That's what I see when I'm in my eyes.
I want to hear the sound of my voice.
I want to hear the
sound of my voice.
Need any help unpacking all this stuff?
Sure, but only if you're not busy.
Seriously, ain't she cute?
I got you a little gift.
No way, you shouldn't have.
You guys suck.
Are you having fun hanging
out here with everyone?
Yes, and the cherry blossoms are pretty.
Yeah, it's too bad they're almost gone.
Oh, please, there's plenty
left, you spoilsport.
Anyway, we're here with Yui.
That's the important thing.
I still can't believe we
made it happen that fast.
Thank you so much for this, Daddy.
Yeah, Kirito, thank you.
Nah, if you want to thank someone,
thank Yuki for helping me develop it.
Wow!
The real world and the virtual.
I thought the closer they came together,
the better the future would be.
It's like, the more the lines
between these worlds blur,
the more everyone gets
sucked into its darkness.
Yeah, but a lot of people
have been helped by it, too.
If anything, I wish I knew
what Kayaba's master plan was.
I don't know.
Maybe it's our job as
survivors of SAO to find out.
I think you're overthinking things.
Yeah, I guess.
Still, I want to find
out more than ever now.
Even after everything that's happened,
my curiosity's got me hooked.
Although, a part of me
thinks I'm being played here.
That's kind of annoying.
Whatever.
I don't know what's
going to happen tomorrow.
All I know is, I want
to be with you forever.
And I want you to be with me.
I'll stick by you even if you
move halfway across the planet.
Who said anything about moving?
Don't forget to take Mila.
Hey, lovebirds!
Quit making out!
We want to take a photo!
Get over here, guys!
Come on!
Well, shall we?
Okay, Daddy.
Thank you.